http://www.beemstercheese.us/privacy-statement

CLOSE
PRIVACY POLICYCONO USA, Inc. (“Beemster”) is committed to respecting your privacy and the personally identifiable information you may provide to us through our website.This Privacy Policy applies to the Beemster Cheese website and webpages on which it is linked or appears, including www.beemstercheese.us, www.beemster.us,  www.beemster.ca, and www.beemstercheese.ca. Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of, and agreement to, this Privacy Policy and the practices it describes.We collect information from and about you.Anonymous Information. When you visit our sites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged. This includes the server name and IP address through which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site, the pages you access while visiting our site, and the address of the website that linked you to our site. We use the browsing information automatically logged by our servers primarily to help us administer and improve our website. We may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about our website to advertisers, potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. This information is not personally identifiable.Personally Identifiable Information. You can visit and browse the public portions of our website without disclosing personally identifiable information about yourself.  On the other hand, if you choose to use our website to directly communicate with us or search for locations near you where you can find our products, you may offer and we may collect personally identifiable information about you. The personally identifiable information that we may collect varies depending on how you use our site and what information you choose to enter.  For example, we may collect your name, email address, zip code and other information you provide on the contact form on our website. Where possible, we indicate which information is required and which is optional. You always have the option of not providing us any information; you may exercise this option by choosing not to use the feature that requires submission of information you would rather not share.Email and Other Voluntary Communications. You may choose to communicate with us through email, via our website, by telephone, in writing, or through other means. We may collect information you provide through such communications, as well as any other personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us.Any information we collect may be kept by us in a general file or files or in a file specific to you or your company or companies. We may retain such information indefinitely.We use information as disclosed and described here.We, along with others who provide services to us, use the personally identifiable information we collect primarily for purposes that include:Improving our website, including tailoring it to users’ preferences;Responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions;Maintaining the security and integrity of our systems; andCommunicating information about our products, special offers and promotions.In rare instances, when necessary to protect your interests, we will send communications related to the security or the administration of our website. We may share information with certain third parties.We never sell your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you. We may, however, use unaffiliated service providers to help us maintain and operate our website or to otherwise support the operation of our business, including but not limited to data analysis and marketing. We may also share personally identifiable information with our business partners. For example, we may share personally identifiable information with third parties who co-sponsor a promotion with us.We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties if required by law or if we believe, in our sole discretion, that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights or property of Beemster or its affiliates, its customers, vendors or suppliers. We may also share information with any successor to all or part of our business. For example, if part of our business is sold, we may provide our customer list as part of that transaction.We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of external linked websites.Our websites and social media pages may contain links to other websites, including those of our partners or advertisers. Inclusion of such links does not indicate or imply that we endorse those other websites or their content, nor does it function as an extension of this privacy policy. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites, even if you follow a link from one of our pages to access such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites before you provide personally identifiable information to or through them.We may use tracking tools to enhance and personalize your experience.Our servers, or the servers of companies that we use to operate this site, may place a cookie, web beacon, pixel tag or other similar device (collectively, “tracking tools”), on your computer in order to allow you to use our website and to personalize or streamline your experience.  Third parties, such as advertising agencies, advertisers and social medial platforms, may use tracking tools to collect or receive information from our website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide targeted advertisements (discussed further below).  You are likely to encounter similar tracking tools across the Internet, including on websites to which our website provides links. We do not control the use of tracking tools on third parties’ websites.Cookies. A “cookie,” or other similar device, is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize your computer while you are on our website, help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you.  The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of our website. Most cookies are session cookies; that is, they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a browsing session. However, some persistent cookies can also be useful in preserving information between sessions. Most web browsers have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. You are always free to prevent cookies from being sent, if your browser permits. Note that blocking or rejecting cookies on individual websites through your browser settings will not stop all forms of tracking, including flash cookies. To control flash cookies, which we may use on our website from time to time, you can go here.Pixel Tag: Pixel tags are tiny graphic images that tell us what parts of our website you have visited or measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our site. They are one type of non-cookie tracking technology.  Pixel tags can be used to help us determine what email format your email program can read and when you have opened an email message from us.  Pixel tags can also be used, in conjunction with third-party advertising companies and platforms, to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf.  For example, we use Facebook pixel to identify users of both the Beemster website and Facebook to deliver content to you on their social media platform.  Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies such as Pixel tags.  Browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on the use of Pixel tags or other non-cookie tracking tools.We may work with other companies to tailor online advertising to your interests.We may work with online advertising companies and advertising agencies to show you relevant and useful ads based on the use of tracking tools described above. This may include ads served on our website. It may also include ads served on other companies’ sites and on social media platforms. These ads may be based on information collected by us pursuant to this Privacy Policy or third parties pursuant to their privacy policies. Ads may be selected for you based on your activities on our website or on third party sites and platforms. This type of advertising is called “online behavioral advertising.”  Through online behavioral advertising, third-party companies use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. Third-party companies may use non-cookie tracking tools to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity, including your activities on our website. These technologies may be used directly on this website.To opt out of direct marketing or to request that we delete personally identifiable information that you have voluntarily shared with us, please send your request via our website contact form.To learn more about online behavioral advertising, consult the educational materials provided by the Digital Advertising Alliance and the Network Advertising Initiative, both of which are self-regulatory associations of third-party digital advertising companies.  To opt out of having your online behavior collected for advertising purposes, click here (Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out) or here (Network Advertising Initiative opt-out). Additionally, certain third-party platforms provide consumers with the ability to opt-out of receiving interest-based ads on their platforms. For example, to opt out of Google’s collection of your online behavior for advertising purposes, visit the Ad Settings page. Choices you make using any of these services or settings are typically browser and device specific.  To effectively limit collection of online behavior information for advertising purposes, you may need to perform opt-outs and settings updates on all browsers and devices that you use. We provide this information only to help you have a greater degree of control over marketing directed to you.  We are not responsible for the operation or efficacy of these services.We have standard measures in place to guard your personally identifiable information, but even these are not foolproof.We maintain standard security measures to guard your personally identifiable information. Please be aware, however, that the Internet is never 100% secure. Even companies in the business of online data security experience breaches that lead to the inadvertent disclosure of users’ personally identifiable and sensitive information. We cannot promise that your use of our site will be completely safe. Any information or message that you send through the Internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.You also have a significant role in protecting your information and must keep your usernames, passwords, and other unique and personally identifiable information private. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet, including when communicating with us.  If you believe you need to share sensitive information with us, you may feel safer doing so over the phone.  If so, you may call the number listed at the bottom of this policy.Our websites, apps, and social media pages are meant for adults, not young children.We expect that users of our websites, apps, and social media pages are over the age of 13.  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 may have given us information, you can contact us via the contact form to determine what, if any, information was collected and to request that we modify or delete it. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark inquiries pertaining to disclosure of personally identifiable information by children: “COPPA Information Request.”We may make changes to this Privacy Policy.We reserve the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. We will not make any material change to the terms of this policy that applies retroactively and is adverse to users’ interests. Whenever we make changes to our privacy policy, we will post an updated copy on our website.We are happy to answer your questions about your privacy and our website.If you have questions about this privacy policy, our information practices, or your dealings with Beemster, or to opt out of receiving communications from us, please contact us via the contact form. You can also write to or call us at:Beemster1 Atalanta PlazaElizabeth, New Jersey 07206(908) 372-6024Effective date:  October 3, 2017
Change Your Language
English
FR-CA
Home
Recipes
Our Cheeses
Meet Beemster
The Latest
